filecroco.com 2019-04-21

# Privacy Policy - Filecroco

At FileCroco **we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important.** This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by FileCroco.com and how we use it. **No effort is made to identify individuals without their knowledge**.

####  **LOG FILES**

When a user requests pages from FileCroco.com web site, our servers automatically recognize the domain name and the IP address. We collect the domain names, browser types, refferit pages, exit pages, IP addresses in order to aggregate information on the pages users access or visit. This information is collected solely for statistical purposes and **is not used to identify individuals**. Whenever the identity of a visitor is recorded we will clearly indicate the purpose of the request before the information is requested.

####  **COOKIES**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user hard disk drive containing information about him. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Some of our partners use cookies on our site (for example, Google Adsense). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies. Please refer to the privacy policies of the above mentioned network for details.

Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). Alternatively, users can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).

FileCroco.com may also use other advertising networks (other than Google AdSense), whose privacy policies will always be listed on their respective sites. Most of these companies belong to the Network Advertising Initiative. Our visitors may opt-out of behavioral advertising meathods by visiting [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

####  **SECURITY**

This web site takes every precaution to protect all our users information. When users submit sensitive information via the web site, your information is protected both online and off-line. Our registration/order form will never asks users to enter sensitive information such as credit card number and/or social security number.

####  **UNSOLICITED COMMUNICATION**

FileCroco.com **will not use your e-mail address** in order to send you any kind of unsolicited or promotional mail.

####  **CONSENT**

By using FileCroco.com, **you hereby consent** to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

####  **UPDATE**

Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page.

 **Last updated: Saturday, February 16, 2019**.
